<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>面對挑戰 on 寶可夢扮演2.0 Pokerole</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/</link><description>Recent content in 面對挑戰 on 寶可夢扮演2.0 Pokerole</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zhtw</language><copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright><atom:link href="https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>劇情設計</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/session-settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/session-settings/</guid><description>面對挑戰 在寶可夢的世界中，訓練家將會面對許多的挑戰。
在這個章節，我們將會提供你一些關於故事情節和長期戰役的想法與框架，善用它們做為你與朋友們一起遊戲的靈感吧。
以下是一些你可以選擇的遊戲聚會設定：
⬛ 本周劇集 一次聚會就是一個完整的冒險故事。
這可以是與你的寶可夢一起幫助有需要人們的輕快物語、在夜晚探索洞窟以及其中隱藏的秘密、一場耗費心力的特訓過程、或者是努力尋找某種特定的寶可夢好完成你的寶可夢圖鑑。
這種形式既簡單且適合新手，你只需要創造出符合玩家們訓練家階級的故事遭遇，作為考驗他們能力的挑戰就好。
做為靈感參考， 你也可以看看短篇寓言故事或寶可夢的動畫影集。你甚至可以重演其中一些集數的情境，並看看你和你的朋友們是否會得到不一樣的結果！
讓故事單純但意義深刻。
冒險中的一切都將在聚會尾聲時跟著圓滿結束。
⬛ 對抗勁敵/邪惡組織 有些討厭鬼總是想針對你，讓你惱怒困擾；而有些則投身犯罪集團，到處製造混亂。
你和你的玩家們可以採用「本周劇集」的形式去對抗玩家們的勁敵或甚至不同地區的邪惡組織。
這可能會是一場與「小茂」的友誼賽、或也許是與偵探一起搜查揭露罪犯的邪惡計畫並將他們統統繩之以法。
要花多長的篇幅去處理訓練家們與勁敵或邪惡組織之間的衝突，將由你來決定。這也許會是時不時發生的遭遇、也可能是他們人生中重要的使命。
你可能會在某次聚會中遭遇他們，接著在兩到三次聚會之後才又再次看見他們的蹤影；或者他們可能會在每一次聚會中反覆出現，嘗試毀了你們訓練家的好日子。
⬛ 寶可夢聯盟挑戰 寶可夢聯盟為訓練家們提供了各種不同的挑戰，其中一些包括：
道館館主挑戰 新手訓練家能夠藉著正確的戰術策略來挑戰道館館主，而老練的訓練家則會需要證明自己擁有足以贏得最後一枚徽章的實力。
你可以選擇直接遊玩特定的道館對戰賽，或者從挑戰道館的整個旅途開始遊戲。畢竟，前往下一個道館所在地的旅途本身就是一場精彩的冒險了！
年度錦標賽挑戰 如果你成功在一年內蒐集到 8 枚道館徽章，那麼你將會被邀請參加該地區的年度錦標賽。在那裏，你將備授予「菁英訓練家」的頭銜，並有機會跟該地區最強大的寶可夢們對戰。在戰鬥場地不斷改變的官方對戰中，大量的觀眾們將為你的戰鬥喝采歡呼或噓聲倒讚。確保你竭盡全力，因為只有贏家才能把獎杯帶回家。
冠軍之路挑戰 如果你在著名的年度錦標賽中奪得了前５名的殊榮，那麼你將獲准前往冠軍之路──這是個充滿危險的可怕迷宮。這將是一段漫長的征途，你會需要使出渾身解數來穿過這個地區最最危險的區域。
⬛ 寶可夢世界的傳說 受夠人類和他們繁瑣的事務了嗎？如果你想要真正的動作、刺激、和危險，那麼你就必須追尋那些謠言和傳說，深入那些人類尚未涉足的世界邊陲。在那裏，你將發現倒你無法掌握的力量。你是否能直面它？又是否能夠馴服它？透過超級進化、極巨型態和超極巨型態來讓你的冒險升級，並藉著通過傳奇英雄的諸島巡禮來將Z招式的力量握在手中。
如果就連這些都無法滿足你的話，那麼昇華到「傳說階級」吧，這是個專屬於傳說級寶可夢與那些受祂們青睞的人們的崇高位置。
每個傳說級寶可夢本身都可以做為維繫一整個戰役的主題：從關於祂們存在本身的偶然線索開始，一路進展到你們這個世代最偉大的發現。
要記住，傳說級寶可夢並不是那種做為迷宮底層大魔王的毫無理智的野獸。祂們全都有著明確的個性、以及祂們各自的行事動機。
你在寶可夢圖鑑上看到的不過是祂們最弱小時的狀態數據，來瞧瞧你是否夠膽面對發揮出全力的祂們吧！
祂們既不是人類，更不是尋常的寶可夢，祂們的存在與力量超乎了這個世界和其中的一切。
祂們會是盟友、還是敵人？這都將取決於你們的故事而定。</description></item><item><title>勁敵系統（可選規則）</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/rival-system/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/rival-system/</guid><description>勁敵系統（可選規則） 俗話說：「你表現越好，就有越多人希望看到你失敗」。而你的勁敵就是這群人中最糟糕的那一個。
無論好壞，無論相熟已否，勁敵總是領先你一步，他們在你行走的道路上出現，提醒著你無論你多麼努力，你也永遠無法像他們一樣優秀。
你的勁敵不僅僅是個需要克服的障礙，他們的存在或許描繪出了一個與你角色相同但卻往錯誤方向發展的本質；或者，他們可能與你的角色完全相反。他們比你更強大、更聰明、更有魅力，且他們也清楚知道這一點。
在你的旅途中，他們會把握每一個機會使你的人生變得艱難，他們有資格把你搞得一團糟，並且每一次都表現得比你更加出色。然而，也許，只是也許，如果你設法克服了你自己所有的弱點，那麼你也許能夠一勞永逸地戰勝他們。
當你創建你的角色時，你也同時創建你的勁敵。
勁敵角色的創建與發展 下列這些數據將透過隨機的方式決定，但在說書人的允許下，你也可以直接決定它們。
在創建勁敵角色時，選擇 1 種態度。 在創建勁敵角色時，選擇 1 種關係。 在創建勁敵角色時，選擇 1 種背景。 在創建勁敵角色時，選擇 1 項異質特性。
你的勁敵會在 初學者、業餘者、菁英、專家、大師、和冠軍階級時額外獲得 1 項異質特性。 決定你勁敵的寶可夢。
牠們必須要比玩家的寶可夢更強大。 勁敵的階級永遠比玩加角色的階級高一階。 ⬛ 態度 Attitudes 善良 混蛋 虛偽 嫉妒 邪惡 ⬛ 關係 Relationship 親戚 - 家庭競爭關係是最糟糕的了…… 朋友 - 友好的競爭關係。 神秘 - 這傢伙到底是誰？ 惡霸 - 他會為了娛樂自己而折磨你。 死敵 - 他執著於看到你的毀滅。 ⬛ 背景 Backgrounds 勁敵是優秀的訓練家，他們有著豐富的背景故事來合理化他們那些強大的技能。
珍獸黑客 Hax0rus 你勁敵的寶可夢也許不是透過合法手段獲得的。牠們是色違品種，且超級稀有。
潮酷守則 Rule of Tenta-Cool 你的勁敵生來就是個明星，他的社交特質和社交類技能數值全都為最大值，並因此相當出名。他總是說著關於你的謊話，且每個人都相信他，就連你的家人和最要好的朋友也是。</description></item><item><title>征服寶可夢聯盟</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/pokemon-league/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/pokemon-league/</guid><description>Conquering the Pokémon League Every Trainer’s dream is to participate at least once in the intense adventure that is the Pokémon League Challenge. A grand scale journey across an entire region to train and prove your skills. All of the greatest trainers have made this journey and it is said to be the only way to become the strongest.
During the Pokémon League Challenge you will face a great amount of danger to test your skills as a trainer, the power of your Pokémon, your own survival ability, and your intelligence and wits.</description></item><item><title>超級進化的力量</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/mega-evolution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/mega-evolution/</guid><description>The Power of Mega-Evolution People in Hoenn mention the legendary Pokémon Rayquaza, as the first Pokémon to ever Mega-Evolve; but the first records of Mega-Evolution as we know it today come from Kalos.
The ancestor of a family that still exists to this day, discovered how to harness this god-like power and embed it into energy stones, later called Mega Stones.
Mega-Evolution consists on infusing your Pokémon with the power contained inside the Mega-Stone.</description></item><item><title>英雄巡禮與Z招式</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/z-moves/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/z-moves/</guid><description>The Ritual of the Hero In the Alolan Region, children of a certain age go through a coming-of-age ritual where they embark on a journey to commune with their Pokémon and the land.
Each of the four Islands in Alola has a Legendary Pokémon who acts as a Guardian. Once in a while, they show themselves, urging one of the young to begin the four trials.
With the guidance of the Kahuna’s, the child goes through these tests.</description></item><item><title>神話與傳說</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/myths-and-legends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/myths-and-legends/</guid><description>Myths and Legends from the Pokémon World As you embark on your first journey, Pokémon: The Role Playing Game will deal with some ordinary affairs and people’s everyday lives, their customs, their aspirations, the relevance of Pokémon and your own in this beautiful and innocent world.
It’s a time to learn about teamwork, leadership, friendship, camaraderie and valor. A journey about pursuing your dreams, climbing to the top, and realizing that you are able to do anything you want if you persevere and work together.</description></item><item><title>傳說階級（可選規則）</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/legendary-ranking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/legendary-ranking/</guid><description>Legendary Ranking (Optional) Pokémon: The Roleplaying Game is mainly focused on low Adventure, it deals with the comings and goings of regular people’s lives and their relationship with nature and Pokémon. However, there is a larger mythology in this world.
Here, we open up the door to the universe of High Adventure which extends further away into the primordial forces of creation. These powers manifest on the Pokémon World in a straight-forward fashion, but only the most worthy and brave have the fortitude to comprehend and face the events that will decide the future.</description></item><item><title>超極巨聯盟</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/dynamax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/dynamax/</guid><description>The BIG Leagues Galarian region is home to a strange phenomenon not seen anywhere else in the world.
In their wild areas is not that rare to find giant Pokémon on a rampage. It seems there are certain underground deposits of energy called “Power Spots” will make a Pokémon grow to an enormous size, you’ll recognize them as tall pillars of red light coming out of the ground.
This is known as the Dynamax phenomenon, and it doesn’t stop there, some Pokémon are so sensitive to this strange energy that upon harnessing it they won’t only increase their size but also modify their appearance and use even more powerful moves, this is called Gigantamax Form.</description></item></channel></rss>