<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>面對挑戰 on 寶可夢扮演2.0 Pokerole</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/</link><description>Recent content in 面對挑戰 on 寶可夢扮演2.0 Pokerole</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zhtw</language><copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright><atom:link href="https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>劇情設計</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/session-settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/session-settings/</guid><description>面對挑戰 There are many challenges for a Trainer within the world of Pokémon.
In this section of the book, we’ll give you some ideas and frameworks for episodic tales and campaigns. Use them as inspiration for your games with your friends.
These are some settings you can choose for your Role playing sessions:
⬛ Episode of the week A whole adventure in a single session. It can be some light hearted fun about helping people in need with the aid of your Pokémon, an evening exploring a cave and its secrets, an exhausting Training session, or the search for a specific Pokémon to complete your Pokémon encyclopedia.</description></item><item><title>勁敵系統（可選規則）</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/rival-system/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/rival-system/</guid><description>Rival System (Optional) It is said “As you get better, more people will want to see you fail”. Your Rival is the worst of those people.
Good or bad, known or unknown, a Rival is always one step ahead and they show up on your path to remind you that it doesn’t matter how hard you work, you’ll never be as good as them.
Your Rival is more than an obstacle, they might portray the same essence as your character but for all the wrong reasons or they may be your complete opposite.</description></item><item><title>征服寶可夢聯盟</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/pokemon-league/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/pokemon-league/</guid><description>Conquering the Pokémon League Every Trainer’s dream is to participate at least once in the intense adventure that is the Pokémon League Challenge. A grand scale journey across an entire region to train and prove your skills. All of the greatest trainers have made this journey and it is said to be the only way to become the strongest.
During the Pokémon League Challenge you will face a great amount of danger to test your skills as a trainer, the power of your Pokémon, your own survival ability, and your intelligence and wits.</description></item><item><title>超級進化的力量</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/mega-evolution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/mega-evolution/</guid><description>The Power of Mega-Evolution People in Hoenn mention the legendary Pokémon Rayquaza, as the first Pokémon to ever Mega-Evolve; but the first records of Mega-Evolution as we know it today come from Kalos.
The ancestor of a family that still exists to this day, discovered how to harness this god-like power and embed it into energy stones, later called Mega Stones.
Mega-Evolution consists on infusing your Pokémon with the power contained inside the Mega-Stone.</description></item><item><title>英雄巡禮與Z招式</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/z-moves/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/z-moves/</guid><description>The Ritual of the Hero In the Alolan Region, children of a certain age go through a coming-of-age ritual where they embark on a journey to commune with their Pokémon and the land.
Each of the four Islands in Alola has a Legendary Pokémon who acts as a Guardian. Once in a while, they show themselves, urging one of the young to begin the four trials.
With the guidance of the Kahuna’s, the child goes through these tests.</description></item><item><title>神話與傳說</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/myths-and-legends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/myths-and-legends/</guid><description>Myths and Legends from the Pokémon World As you embark on your first journey, Pokémon: The Role Playing Game will deal with some ordinary affairs and people’s everyday lives, their customs, their aspirations, the relevance of Pokémon and your own in this beautiful and innocent world.
It’s a time to learn about teamwork, leadership, friendship, camaraderie and valor. A journey about pursuing your dreams, climbing to the top, and realizing that you are able to do anything you want if you persevere and work together.</description></item><item><title>傳說階級（可選規則）</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/legendary-ranking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/legendary-ranking/</guid><description>Legendary Ranking (Optional) Pokémon: The Roleplaying Game is mainly focused on low Adventure, it deals with the comings and goings of regular people’s lives and their relationship with nature and Pokémon. However, there is a larger mythology in this world.
Here, we open up the door to the universe of High Adventure which extends further away into the primordial forces of creation. These powers manifest on the Pokémon World in a straight-forward fashion, but only the most worthy and brave have the fortitude to comprehend and face the events that will decide the future.</description></item><item><title>超極巨聯盟</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/dynamax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/challenges-ahead/dynamax/</guid><description>The BIG Leagues Galarian region is home to a strange phenomenon not seen anywhere else in the world.
In their wild areas is not that rare to find giant Pokémon on a rampage. It seems there are certain underground deposits of energy called “Power Spots” will make a Pokémon grow to an enormous size, you’ll recognize them as tall pillars of red light coming out of the ground.
This is known as the Dynamax phenomenon, and it doesn’t stop there, some Pokémon are so sensitive to this strange energy that upon harnessing it they won’t only increase their size but also modify their appearance and use even more powerful moves, this is called Gigantamax Form.</description></item></channel></rss>