<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>開始遊戲 on 寶可夢扮演2.0 Pokerole</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/starting-the-game/</link><description>Recent content in 開始遊戲 on 寶可夢扮演2.0 Pokerole</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zhtw</language><copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright><atom:link href="https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/starting-the-game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>創建角色</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/starting-the-game/create-character/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/starting-the-game/create-character/</guid><description>Creating a Character In Pokémon the Role Playing Game, you must create a Pokémon Trainer also called a Character. This persona will be your avatar inside the story.
You’ll choose a starting Pokémon too, both are very important choices, remember that your Pokémon are often a reflection of your trainer’s ersonality and aspirations.
When creating a character, choose something that’s fun to play, allow yourself to dream, be silly and laugh at your most crazy ideas.</description></item><item><title>創建寶可夢</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/starting-the-game/create-pokemon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/starting-the-game/create-pokemon/</guid><description>Creating a Pokémon A Pokémon will be commanded by their trainer but within the game, they won’t be controlled by a player.
It’s part of the storyteller’s job to play and tell you how your Pokémon reacts to its surroundings or how it communicates with you.
Think about it as having a pet, you can ask it to follow you or to stop chewing the carpet, but you are not really inside its mind.</description></item><item><title>心理/物理/社交特質</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/starting-the-game/attributes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/starting-the-game/attributes/</guid><description>Mental and Physical Attributes Your Character will interact with the world using his Attributes and Skills, They are measured using Points within a Character Sheet, each point represents one die you can roll for that attribute should your action call for it. Attributes can be rolled on their own to perform mundane tasks or they can be combined with skills if you want to do complex and incredible feats.
The scores range from 1 to 5 in humans, but some of the stronger Pokémon can exceed that number.</description></item><item><title>技能</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/starting-the-game/skills/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/starting-the-game/skills/</guid><description>Skills and Extras You will be needing Skills to make your adventure easier and help you go through many situations. Your Pokémon can learn a few on their own, but you can also train them so they can grow stronger.
A Skill is a varied compendium of applied knowledge. They can cover a broad number of situations, they don&amp;rsquo;t have to be specific to a certain discipline .
There are so many different skills in the world, that it is impossible to practice or master most of them.</description></item></channel></rss>