<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>寶可夢招式 on 寶可夢扮演2.0 Pokerole</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/pokemon-moves/</link><description>Recent content in 寶可夢招式 on 寶可夢扮演2.0 Pokerole</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zhtw</language><copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright><atom:link href="https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/pokemon-moves/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>招式的規則</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/pokemon-moves/basic-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/pokemon-moves/basic-rules/</guid><description>Pokemon Moves It’s more important to master the cards you’re holding than to complain about the ones your opponents were dealt.
-Grimsley
Pokémon inhabit the vast majority of this world and they protect themselves using wondrous powers. They are able to call upon a certain kind of energy and shape it to attack foes or weaken them; some Pokémon can even use their powers to strengthen or heal themselves and others.</description></item><item><title>招式效果標誌</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/pokemon-moves/effect-types/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/pokemon-moves/effect-types/</guid><description>招式效果標誌 在這個章節中羅列了許許多多的效果標誌。它們是協助你快速參照效果的圖標，用來說明招式的目標、命中率、以及最重要的：招式的效果。
大部分的效果標誌的意義都相當不言自明，且能幫上你很大的忙。
留意你招式的效果。
如果你能學會組合它們，那它們將會成為你邁向勝利的關鍵。
分類圖示 {@icon moveType|l|physical}
物理招式
物理招式 會被「防禦」數值抵抗。它們通常會是近距離攻擊。
有些物理招式可以造成遠距離攻擊，它們會被標註為 遠程招式。
{@icon moveType|l|special}
特殊招式
特殊招式 會被「特防」數值抵抗。它們永遠會是遠程招式。
{@icon moveType|l|support}
變化招式
變化招式 並不會造成任何直接傷害。
機率骰 這標誌代表著該招式的效果是否發動的機率。
標誌上的數字代表著你需要用來擲骰判定的機率骰的數量。
{@icon dice|l|1}{@icon dice|l|2}{@icon dice|l|3}{@icon dice|l|4}{@icon dice|l|5}
如果至少有一個機率骰骰出了 {@icon rdice|s|6|normal} 的結果，那麼該效果就會發動。有時候機率骰會出現在異常狀態框裡面，用來表示造成該異常狀態的機率，如下圖範例所示：
{@icon frame|flinch|畏縮|number|d3}
絕不生效/永遠生效 ✖
當某個效果帶有這個標誌，代表該效果的目標絕不會被影響。
✔
當某個效果帶有這個標誌，代表該效果的目標永遠會被影響。
這些標誌會出現在效果框之中，如下圖範例所示：
{@icon frame|flinch|畏縮|never} 永遠會畏縮
{@icon frame|flinch|畏縮|always} 絕不會畏縮
降低命中率 {@icon frame|accuracy|命中|down|X}
該招式的命中判定將會扣除指定數量的成功骰。
關於更多詳情，請參見「勝利策略」章節。
目標 這些標誌說明了誰會受到這個招式的影響。
綠色目標標誌 被用於使用者或牠的隊友：
紅色目標標誌 被用於敵人：
{@icon target|l|self} 使用者</description></item><item><title>Z招式</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/pokemon-moves/z-moves/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/pokemon-moves/z-moves/</guid><description>Z-Moves Ancient People from the Alola Region had traditional rituals and dances to boost their fighting spirits and comune with their Pokémon. The Kahuna chiefs and their Pokémon wore special jewels with crystals that shone with energy ready to be unleashed to defend their people.
These Jewels are now known as Z-Crystals, if you and your Pokémon hold them and perform the ritual dances, you’ll be able to use what is known as a Z-Move to give a taste of the power of friendship to those who oppose you.</description></item><item><title>極巨招式</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/pokemon-moves/max-moves/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/pokemon-moves/max-moves/</guid><description>Max Moves Dynamax and G-Max Pokémon
So you think you are ready for the BIG leagues?
When a Pokémon is under the Effects of the Dynamax Phenomenon it grows not just on size but on power as well and Max Moves will ad an extra layer of complexity to your strategy!
Rules for Max Moves Max Moves can only be used while a Pokémon is under the Effects of Dynamax or Gigantamax.</description></item><item><title>常見問題</title><link>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/pokemon-moves/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hazmole.github.io/PokeRole/docs/pokemon-moves/faq/</guid><description>Frequently Asked Questions Can I Target an Ally with a Move that Targets a Foe? Yes, you can. Very rarely you’ll find a use to it, but sometimes it’s worth the effort, such as with Swagger or an Electric Move on a Pokémon with Volt Absorb.
Can my Pokémon Target itself with a Move that Targets an Ally or a Foe? No, you can’t. Most Moves that target an Ally or a Foe are just impossible to be employed on the User, such as After You or Helping Hand, you need another target to benefit from this power.</description></item></channel></rss>